SEBASTIAN PAULO HALOHO

Yogyakarta, Indonesia | bastianhalo19@gmail.com | +6288228655310 | LinkedIn | GitHub | GitLab

Summary

I have experience building websites using HTML/CSS, PHP, JavaScript, and processing data using MySQL. I also have experience as a bootcamp participant at Codemasters Id intensively by understanding Full Stack development material, namely React JS, Node Js, JavaScript, Express Js, and others. I am currently working as a Full Stack Developer in an aviation company. With the skills I have, I remain open to career opportunities to expand my experience and connections.

Skill

HTML, CSS, SASS/SCSS, JavaScript, React Js, Next Js, Node Js, React Native, MongoDB, Express Js, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Vue, MySQL, Git, GCP, RESTful API.

Education

Codemasters Id Bootcamp Program

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023

Full Stack Development program

Study and explore front-end mobile development material using the React Native framework, back-end development material using Node JS with Express JS and deepen website development material using React JS.

Final Project

- <u>Toyota Trust Mobile App</u>: Building a mobile application for selling and trading cars from the supervisor's side using
 the React Native framework which aims to be the final project in React Native material at the bootcamp at
 Codemasters.
- <u>Codemasters Admin Web Clone</u>: Build a website with a design from the Codemasters admin website by imitating the features and functions of the website using React Js, Node Js, Express Js, and MongoDB.
- Healthy Foods API: Building an API and database flow from the backend side for a healthy food sales application
 as a task of understanding the back-end engineer.

Universitas Teknologi Yogyakarta

Sep 2017 - Aug 2022

Sistem Informasi - S1

- Learn about the workflow that exists in the system with information that has value. Develop an application that contains an information system with a clear structure and can be implemented in business.
- Understanding and experience developing websites using HTML, JavaScript, CSS, PHP, and MySQL programming.

Experiences

PT ASI Pudjiastuti Aviation (Susi Air)

Oct 2023 - Apr 2024

Full Stack Developer

- Responsible for fixing bugs on the website.
- Carry out regular website maintenance to avoid bugs and unwanted data leaks.
- Update web features and functions if needed.
- Responsible for integrating and maintenance API and databases.

PT Medika Digital Nusantara

Jul 2023 - Sep 2023

Freelance Customer Service (Technical)

- Responding to client queries in a timely and accurate way, via phone, email, or chat.
- Identifying client needs and helping customers use specific features.
- Communicate with the development team to improve and update the features that clients want.
- Update our internal databases with information about technical issues and useful discussions with clients.
- Follow up with clients to ensure their technical issues are resolved.